{"question":"What has four sides?","choices":["Square","circle","triangle","hexagon"],"answer":"Square","explaination":"A square has four equal sides","type":"PICTURE","category":"SHAPES","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which is round?","choices":["Square","circle","Triangle","Rectangle"],"answer":"circle","explaination":"A square has four equal sides","type":"PICTURE","category":"SHAPES","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which is a square?","choices":["Square","circle","triangle","rectangle"],"answer":"Square","explaination":"A circle is round","type":"PICTURE","category":"SHAPES","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which shape is red?","choices":["Square","circle","triangle","rectangle"],"answer":"Square","explaination":"A square has four equal sides","type":"PICTURE","category":"COLORS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which is a triangle?","choices":["Square","circle","triangle","rectangle"],"answer":"triangle","explaination":"A triangle has three sides","type":"PICTURE","category":"SHAPES","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which is a dog?","choices":["dog","giraffe","deer","elephant"],"answer":"dog","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE","category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which is an elephant?","choices":["dog","giraffe","whale","elephant"],"answer":"elephant","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE","category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which is a giraffe?","choices":["deer","giraffe","whale","elephant"],"answer":"giraffe","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE","category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which is a whale?","choices":["dog","giraffe","whale","elephant"],"answer":"whale","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE","category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which country is not in Europe","choices":["Iceland","Italy","Greenland","Romania"],"answer":"Greenland","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"GEOGRAPHY","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which continent contains the equator?","choices":["Africa","Europe","North America","Antarctica"],"answer":"Africa","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"GEOGRAPHY","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"What continent contains Egypt?","choices":["Africa","Europe","Asia","South America"],"answer":"Africa","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"GEOGRAPHY","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which planet is closest to the Sun?","choices":["Mercury","Venus","Earth","Mars"],"answer":"Mercury","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"PLANETS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which planet is the largest in the Solar System?","choices":["Saturn","Earth","The Sun","Jupiter"],"answer":"Jupiter","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"PLANETS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which planet is made of gas?","choices":["Saturn","Neptune","Mars","Earth"],"answer":"Saturn","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"PLANETS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which one is not a vegetable?","choices":["Apple","Broccoli","Mushroom","Onion"],"answer":"Apple","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"FOOD","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which fruit is yellow?","choices":["Apple","Banana","Kiwi","grapes"],"answer":"Banana","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"COLORS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which fruit is the biggest?","choices":["Papaya","Peach","Watermelon","Cherry"],"answer":"Watermelon","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"FOOD","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which shape does not have 4 edges?","choices":["Square","Circle","Rectangle","Diamond"],"answer":"Circle","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"SHAPES","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which country is the largest?","choices":["France","Russia","Germany","India"],"answer":"Russia","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"GEOGRAPHY","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which planet is farthest from the sun?","choices":["Earth","Venus","Neptune","Mars"],"answer":"Neptune","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"PLANETS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which of animal is the biggest?","choices":["Kangaroo","Bunny","Giraffe","Elephant"],"answer":"Elephant","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"How many legs does a spider have?","choices":["2","6","7","8"],"answer":"8","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which is not a Disney Character?","choices":["Donald Duck","Goofy","Mickey Mouse","Dexter"],"answer":"Dexter","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which is the largest continent in the world?","choices":["Africa","Europe","Asia","Antarctica"],"answer":"Asia","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"GEOGRAPHY","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which continent is the coldest?","choices":["Australia","Africa","Europe","Antarctica"],"answer":"Antarctica","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"GEOGRAPHY","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which animal has stripes","choices":["Horse","Zebra","Giraffe","Hippo"],"answer":"Zebra","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which food is a root?","choices":["Tomato","Radish","Corn","Pepper"],"answer":"Radish","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"FOOD","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"What measures length?","choices":["Calculator","Ruler","Scale","Pencil"],"answer":"Ruler","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"STATIONARY","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"What instrument is a brass?","choices":["Violin","Piano","Trumpet","Flute"],"answer":"Trumpet","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"INSTRUMENTS","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which one is not a planet?","choices":["Neptune","Saturn","The Sun","Earth"],"answer":"The Sun","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"PLANETS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"What shape has 3 sides?","choices":["Square","circle","triangle","rectangle"],"answer":"triangle","explaination":"A triangle has three sides","type":"PICTURE","category":"SHAPES","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which fruit is green?","choices":["apple","grapes","banana","kiwi"],"answer":"kiwi","explaination":"A kiwi has is green on the inside","type":"PICTURE","category":"COLORS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which is a Deer?","choices":["dog","giraffe","deer","elephant"],"answer":"deer","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE","category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Where do fishes live?","choices":["Ocean","Sky","Desert","Tree"],"answer":"Ocean","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"ANIMALS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which of the following do you use to write on paper","choices":["Pencil","Ruler","Scale","Eraser"],"answer":"Pencil","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"STATIONARY","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which of the following is used for coloring","choices":["crayon","ruler","sharpener","eraser"],"answer":"crayon","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"STATIONARY","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which of the following is not a sense organ","choices":["eyes","nose","skin","hands"],"answer":"hands","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"BODYPARTS","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which organ do you use to smell","choices":["eyes","nose","tongue","ears"],"answer":"nose","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"BODYPARTS","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Identify a violin from the pictures","choices":["violin","guitar","piano","flute"],"answer":"violin","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"INSTRUMENTS","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which of the following is a string instrument","choices":["drums","guitar","piano","flute"],"answer":"guitar","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"INSTRUMENTS","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Identify the planet Saturn","choices":["mercury","saturn","jupiter","earth"],"answer":"saturn","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"PLANETS","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which of the following bodypart is used for hearing sounds","choices":["eye","nose","hand","ear"],"answer":"ear","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"BODYPARTS","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which of the following bodypart is used for walking","choices":["eye","hand","foot","ear"],"answer":"foot","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"BODYPARTS","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which fruit is red?","choices":["apple","banana","grapes","kiwi"],"answer":"apple","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE","category":"COLORS","level":"LEVEL_1"}
{"question":"Which food is a leaf?","choices":["Potato","Radish","Lettuce","Pepper"],"answer":"Lettuce","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"FOOD","level":"LEVEL_2"}
{"question":"Which of the following is used for erasing","choices":["crayon","ruler","sharpener","eraser"],"answer":"eraser","explaination":"","type":"PICTURE", "category":"STATIONARY","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which organ do you use to taste food","choices":["eyes","nose","ears","tongue"],"answer":"tongue","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"BODYPARTS","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which of the following do you use to draw a circle","choices":["Protractor","Scale","Compass","Stapler"],"answer":"Compass","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"STATIONARY","level":"LEVEL_3"}
{"question":"Which food is a stem?","choices":["Tomato","Radish","Corn","Potato"],"answer":"Potato","explaination":"","type":"TEXT", "category":"FOOD","level":"LEVEL_2"}
